[Music]
Hello friends partners and Associates
very very happy to be talking to you
today and very very excited it's a very
special day for all of us
we at ICICI have been investing a big
time on health and I think
and in various interactions with you
we've been saying that we will address
the entire health fair of our customer
when we say the entire Health life cycle
or the sphere we are talking about OPD
products we are talking about ipd
products and also disease management
you remember I think couple of months
back we did a very very strong launch of
OPD program in the in the form of be fit
and today we are very confident both on
the OPD part in terms of cashless and in
ipd we are one of the best in terms of
providing
cashless home services to our customers
and we are very proud of it is
so when we met some of our advisors
we also constituted a board which we
called as the health Advisory Board
where we got together and we said what
else can we do and one of the main
criteria the main feedback that we got
from the market is let's look at
different customer segments and design a
product for each customer segment s
we also did a consumer research and we
said let's create some products for
specific customer products and today is
launch of first such special product
which we call Golden Shield
uh that's the product that we designed
for our elders for our parents for the
family and that's the senior citizen
program as we call it it's a very very
specific segment it has huge potential
almost 15 percent of the Indian
population is between the age group of
60 to 80. which is a big segment and we
thought and of course a lot of feedback
from consumers and our advisors was
let's focus and design a product very
specific for this segment so we went
about on the drawing board and created a
new powerful product called Golden sheet
now this is an excellent product and
some of the USPS of this product are a
good some insured range
competitive pricing
more than that we looked at the segment
and realized that the expenses of this
segment almost 3x than the normal age
group and we thought how do we address
that plus we've seen this segment always
needs a lot of associated programs and
we said how do we address that not just
the ipd can we do something more than
that and two of the unique features that
we put in this product
one is the
besides your hospitalization it takes
care of your emergency assistance it
takes care of your International second
opinion in case
for the disease we help it as injured we
also take care of disease management
which we thought was a very very
critical aspect we help you manage
disease post
hospitalization and even if it's a
chronic disease the disease
how to manage the disease it also has
Health checkup so that's one stronger
aspect the second strong aspect that we
thought would be very very prompt and
appropriate for this customer segment uh
was the assistance when we say
assistance is checking availability of
hospital beds as the engine for those
beds checking Arrangement you know
checking home delivery of medicines
getting you discounts on various
medicines so I think these are very very
unique features which we felt is very
strongly needed by this segment which is
often ignored in the normal health
insurance policies so we thought we will
make a age-specific product and address
a segment which some companies shy away
from but our commitment has always been
we will be across the segment across age
groups and across the life cycle of the
consumer's Health journey and therefore
we launch this product we are very very
excited about this product we feel that
immense potential in terms of Premium
also it has immense value for the
customer so this will create a huge
amount of Goodwill for us and our
advisors and also create huge amount of
stickiness for our customers
so look forward with the you know to
working with each one of you to make
this product a huge success and uh you
know get huge amount of customers to you
and to us thank you very much and all
the best
[Music]